Guide to the Columbia Unoversity Press Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Arranged Files
  - Clark(e) (Box 35)
  - Clark, David Lee (Box 35)
  - Clark, Donald Leinen (Box 35)
  - Clark, Edgar Rogie (Box 35)
  - Clark, Grover (Box 35)
  - Clark, Jane Perry (Box 36)
  - Clark, John Bates (Box 36)
  - Clark, Roy Benjamin (Box 36)
  - Clarke., John Alfred (Box 36)
  - Clarkson, Jesse Dunsmore & Thomas C. Cochran (Box 36)
  - Clas - Claw (Box 36)
  - Cle (Box 36)
  - Clemen(s)(t)(ts) (Box 36)
  - Cleve, Felix M. (Box 36)
  - Cli - Clu (Box 36)
  - Closen, (Baron) Ludwig von (Box 36)
  - Clough, Coryeen (Box 36)
  - Clough, Rosa Trillo (Mrs Shepard. B.) (Box 36)
  - Clough, Shepard. Bancroft (Box 36)
  - Co-Cof (Box 37)
  - Coffin, Berton (Box 37)
  - Coffin, Charles Monroe (Box 37)
  - Coh-Cok (Box 37)
  - Cohen (Box 37)
  - Cohen, Helen Louise (Box 37)
  - Cohen, Lawrence B. (Box 37)
  - Cohen, Percy (Box 37)
  - Cohn, Georg (Box 37)
  - Colt, Cha Guernsey (Box 37)
  - Col - Coig (Box 37)
  - Colbert, Evelyn Speyer (Box 37)
  - Cole (Box 37)
  - Cole, Charles C., Jr. (Box 37)
  - Cole, Charles Woolsey (Box 37)
  - Coleman (Box 37)
  - Coleman, Arthur Prudden (Box 37)
  - Coleman, Johxi Macdonald (Box 37)
  - Coll (Box 38)
  - Collier's (Box 38)
  - Colm - Colu (Box 38)
  - Colson, Percy (Box 38)
  - Coiton, Joel G. (Box 38)
  - Colum, Mary Gunning Maguire (Mrs Padraic). (Box 38)
  - Columbia, Curtis F. (Box 38)
  - Columbia University Alumni Register (Box 38)
  - Columbia University Archives of Philosophy (Box 38)
  - Columbia University Audio-visual survey (Box 38)
  - Columbia University Bicentennial broadcast lectures (Box 38)
  - Columbia University Columbia Biographical Dictionary (Box 38)
  - Columbia University Columbia biological series (Box 38)
  - Columbia University. Center for Mass Communications (Box 39)
  - Columbia University. Center for Mass Communications Special projects (Box 39)
  - Columbia University. Center for Mass Communications Special projects: Educational Films (Box 39)
  - Columbia University. Center for Mass Communications Special projects: Radio Bureau (Box 39)
  - Columbia University. Center for Mass Communications Special projects: Proposals (Box 39)
  - Columbia University. Center for Mass Communications Special projects: Public Health Revolving Fund (Box 39)
  - Columbia University. Center for Mass Communications Special projects: Television Programs (Box 39)
  - Columbia University Charters & statutes (Box 39)
  - Columbia University Columbia Classics (Box 39)
  - Columbia University Club (Box 39)
  - Columbia & Barnard. Glee Club Series (Box 39)
  - Columbia College (Box 39)
  - Columbia College Committee Curriculum Report (Box 39)
  - Columbia University The Columbian (Box 39)
  - Columbia University Columbiana Society (Box 39)
  - Columbia University. Committee on Education Approvals (Box 39)
  - Columbia University. Committee on Education Payments (Box 39)
  - Columbia University Contemporary Civilization: A - D (Box 40)
  - Columbia University Contemporary Civilization: R - S (Box 41)
  - Columbia University Contributions to Anthropology (Box 42)
  - Columbia University Contributions to Oriental History and Philology (Box 42)
  - Columbia University Contributions to Philosophy, Psychology & Education (Box 42)
  - Columbia University Council for Research in the Social Sciences (Box 42)
  - Columbia University Council for Research in the Humanities (Box 42)
  - Columbia University Course in Literature (Box 43)
  - Columbia University Columbia Crown Service Plates (Box 43)
  - Columbia University Dental School (Box 43)
  - Columbia University Dramatic Museum Publications Series (Box 43)
  - Columbia University Dissertations (Box 43)
  - Columbia University Economics dissertation plan (Box 44)
  - Columbia University Educational Films (Box 44)
  - Columbia University Columbia Film Institute (Box 44)
  - Columbia University Columbia Geological Series (Box 44)
  - Columbia University Columbia Geomorphic Studies (Box 44)
  - Columbia University The Germanic Review (Box 44)
  - Columbia University Germanic Studies (Box 44)
  - Columbia University Guide to (Box 44)
  - Columbia University History of (Box 44)
  - Columbia University A History of Columbia in World War II (Box 44)
  - Columbia University Columbia Histories of Latin America (Box 44)
  - Columbia University History of religion lectures (Box 44)
  - Columbia University Columbia Home Front Warbooks (Box 44)
  - Columbia University Home Study Series (Box 44)
  - Columbia University The Independent Journal of Columbia University (Box 45)
  - Columbia University Indo- Iranian Series (Box 45)
  - Columbia University Industrial Engineering (Box 45)
  - Columbia University The Columbia Journal of History (Box 45)
  - Columbia University Columbia Legal Studies (Box 45)
  - Columbia University Libraries (Box 45)
  - Columbia University Lectures on literature (Box 45)
  - Columbia University Lectures on science, philosophy and art (Box 45)
  - Columbia University The Columbia Lippincott gazetteer (Box 45)
  - Columbia University Mechanical Engineering (Box 45)
  - Columbia University Music department (Box 45)
  - Columbia University Oriental Studies (Box 45)
  - Columbia University Pictorial History of Columbia University (Box 45)
  - Columbia University Columbia poetry (Box 45)
  - Columbia University Political Science bibliography (Box 45)
  - Columbia University Columbia University Quarterly (Box 45)
  - Columbia University Radio Club (Box 46)
  - Columbia University Records of Civilization (Box 46)
  - Columbia University Religious education (Box 46)
  - Columbia University Columbia Review anthology (Box 46)
  - Columbia University The review of religion (Box 46)
  - Columbia University The romantic review (Box 46)
  - Columbia University Russian Institute Series (Box 46)
  - Columbia University School of Library Service (Box 46)
  - Columbia University Columbia Slavic Studies (Box 46)
  - Columbia University Social Psychology Series (Box 46)
  - Columbia University Statistical Research Group (Division of War Research) (Box 46)
  - Columbia University Students' Shorter Classics (Box 46A)
  - Columbia University Columbia University Studies in... (Box 46A)
  - Columbia University Columbia Studies in American Culture (Box 46A)
  - Columbia University Columbia Studies in Archeology and Ethnology (Box 46A)
  - Columbia University Columbia University Studies in Comparative Linguistics (Box 46A)
  - Columbia University Columbia University Studies in English and Comparative Literature (Box 46A)
  - Columbia University Columbia Studies in History, Economics, and Public Law (Box 46B)
  - Columbia University Columbia University Studies in Library Service Columbia University Studies in Musicology (Box 46B)
  - Columbia University Columbia University Studies in the History of American Agriculture (Box 47)
  - Columbia University Studies in the history of ideas (Box 47)
  - Columbia University Columbia Studies in the Social Sciences (Box 47)
  - Columbia University Studies of Post-War France (Box 47)
  - Columbia University Summary Reports (Division of War Research) (Box 47)
  - Columbia University Summer Session Announcement (Box 47)
  - Columbia University Symposium on Essential Hypertension (Box 47)
  - Columbia University Syllabus for Sociology (Box 47)
  - Columbia University This week at Columbia (Box 47)
  - Columbia University Columbia University Travel Service (Box 47)
  - Columbia University The Writers Club Bulletin (Box 47)
  - Colwick, Alfred Martin (Box 48)
  - Com (Box 48)
  - Corner, John Preston (Box 48)
  - Commission on Financing Higher Education (Box 48)
  - Community Service Society of New York (Box 48)
  - Con (Box 48)
  - Conant, James Bryant (Box 48)
  - Conant, Martha Pike (Box 48)
  - Conklin, George Newton (Box 48)
  - Conklin, Paul Salisbury (Box 48)
  - Conklin, Robert J. (Box 48)
  - Conn (Box 48)
  - Conner; Connor (Box 48)
  - Conover (Box 48)
  - Cons - Conw (Box 48)
  - Contemporary Developments in Chemistry (Box 48)
  - Coo (Box 49)
  - Cook(e) (Box 49)
  - Coolidge, John Phillips (Box 49)
  - Coon - Coq (Box 49)
  - Coonan, Thomas L. (Box 49)
  - Cooper (Box 49)
  - Cor - Cork (Box 49)
  - Corbett (Box 49)
  - Corr - Cort (Box 49)
  - Cornell (Box 49)
  - Corson, John Jay (Box 49)
  - Corwin, Edward H. L. (Box 49)
  - Cory, Helen May (Box 49)
  - Cos - Cot (Box 49)
  - Cosentini, John Walter (Box 49)
  - Coss, John Jacob (Box 49)
  - Cosse, Margaret Victoria (Box 49)
  - Cou (Box 49)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, Inc. (Box 49)
  - Courtines, Léo Pierre (Box 49)
  - Covell, Jon Carter (Box 50)
  - Cow - Coy (Box 50)
  - Cowan; Cowen (Box 50)
  - Cowan, Laing Gray (Box 50)
  - Cowdrey, Mary Bartlett & Hermann Warner Williams (Box 50)
  - Cox (Box 50)
  - Cra (Box 50)
  - Craig (Box 50)
  - Cramer, Lawrence William (Box 50)
  - Crampton, Henry Edward (Box 50)
  - Crane, William Garrett (Box 50)
  - Crawford (Box 50)
  - Crawford, Henry Paine (Box 50)
  - Cre - Cri (Box 50)
  - Cro - Croo (Box 50)
  - Cros (Box 50)
  - Cross (Box 50)
  - Cross, Harold Livingston (Box 50)
  - Crosten, William Loran (Box 50)
  - Crou - Cru (Box 51)
  - Crouse, Nellis Maynard (Box 51)
  - Crowell, Merle (Box 51)
  - Crowell, Thomas Y., Company (Box 51)
  - Crowley, Joseph (Box 51)
  - Crum, Ralph B. (Box 51)
  - Cu - Cun (Box 51)
  - Culbertson, James Thomas (Box 51)
  - Culver, Henry B. (Box 51)
  - Cumming, Charles Gordon (Box 51)
  - Cur (Box 52)
  - Current problems in American life.. (Box 52)
  - Curti, Merle Eugene (Box 52)
  - Curti(n)(s) (ss) (Box 52)
  - Curtis, Eugene Newton (Box 52)
  - Curtiss, John Shelton (Box 52)
  - Cus - Cuz (Box 52)
  - Cushing, Mary Gertrude (Box 52)
  - Da - Dak (Box 53)
  - Dafoe, John Wesley (Box 53)
  - Dahl, Svend (Box 53)
  - Dahlberg, Gunnar (Box 53)
  - Dahnie, Lena Friedrich (Box 53)
  - Dakin, Arthur Hazard (Box 53)
  - Dal - Dam (Box 53)
  - Dale (Box 53)
  - Dan (Box 53)
  - Dangler, Edward (Box 53)
  - The. Danish Society (Box 53)
  - Danstrup, John (Box 53)
  - Danton, George, Henry (Box 53)
  - Da-Dak (Box 53)
  - Dar - Da (Box 53)
  - Das (Box 53)
  - Daugert, Stanley Matthew (Box 53)
  - Dav - David (Box 54)
  - Davenport (Box 54)
  - David Charles Wendell (Box 54)
  - Davie (Box 54)
  - Davies (Box 54)
  - Davies, Ruth (Box 54)
  - Davila, William (Box 54)
  - Davis (Box 54)
  - Davis, Edwin A (Box 54)
  - Davis, Georgene. Webber (Box 54)
  - Davis, Harriet Ide Eager (Mrs Malcolm W.) (Box 54)
  - Davis, John Aubrey (Box 54)
  - Davis, Rose Mary (Box 54)
  - Dawson (Box 54)
  - Day (Box 54)
  - Day, John (Box 54)
  - Dayton, Eldorous (Box 54)
  - De-Deb (Box 55)
  - Deák, Francis (Box 55)
  - Dearle (Box 55)
  - Dec - Def (Box 55)
  - De Cholnoky, Tibor (Box 55)
  - Deegan, Dorothy Margaret Yost (Box 55)
  - Deg-Dej (Box 55)
  - De Groot, John Henry (Box 55)
  - De Haas, Elsa (Box 55)
  - Dehn, Edgar (Box 55)
  - De Kay, Drake (Box 55)
  - Del (Box 55)
  - Dem (Box 55)
  - Demaree, Albert Lowther (Box 55)
  - Den - Dep (Box 55)
  - De Podwin, Horace John (Box 55)
  - Der - Deu (Box 56)
  - Deutsch (Box 56)
  - Deutsch, Albert (Box 56)
  - Dev-Dey (Box 56)
  - Dewey, Evelyn (Mrs Granville Smith, Jr.) (Box 56)
  - Dewey, John (Box 56)
  - Dewey, Melville (Box 56)
  - Dhaila, M. N. (Box 56)
  - Di - Did (Box 56)
  - Dickson, Arthur (Box 56)
  - Die - Dij (Box 56)
  - Diekhoff, John Siemon (Box 56)
  - Dieterien, Pierre (Box 56)
  - Dil - Dir (Box 56)
  - Dillon, Rorothy Rita (Box 56)
  - Dilworth, Ernest Nevin (Box 56)
  - Dinsmoor, William Bell (Box 56)
  - Directory of medical specialists certified by American boards (Box 57 & 58)
  - Directory of social agencies of the City of New York (Box 59)
  - Dirks, John Edward (Box 60)
  - Dit - Dix (Box 60)
  - Dix, John A. & Leicester C. Lewis (Box 60)
  - Doa - Doe (Box 60)
  - Dobbie, Elliott Van Kirk (Box 60)
  - Dobzhansky, Theodosius Grigorievich (Box 60)
  - Dodd, Charles Harold (Box 60)
  - Dodd, David Le Fevre (Box 60)
  - Dodge (Box 60)
  - Dodge, Guy Howard (Box 60)
  - Doh - Dom (Box 61)
  - Dohr, James Lewis (Box 61)
  - Dombrowski, James A. (Box 61)
  - Don - Donh (Box 61)
  - Doniger, Simon (Box 61)
  - Donn - Doo (Box 61)
  - R.R. Donnelley & Sons (Box 61)
  - Dor - Dot (Box 61)
  - Doshay, Lewis J. (Box 61)
  - Doubleday (Box 61)
  - Douglas (Box 61)
  - Doukas, Kimon Apostolus (Box 61)
  - Dow - Doz (Box 61)
  - Dower, Edward A., Jr. (Box 61)
  - Dowey, Edward A. (Box 61)
  - Dowling; Downing (Box 61)
  - Dra - Dre (Box 61)
  - Drake, Leonard Ayres (Box 61)
  - Dressier. David (Box 61)
  - Dri - Dry (Box 62)
  - Drinker, Henry Sandwith (Box 62)
  - Drinkwater, John (Box 62)
  - Du - Dum (Box 62)
  - Du Bois (Box 62)
  - Due, John Fitzgerald (Box 62)
  - Duey, Philip Alexander (Box 62)
  - Dumbauld, Edward (Box 62)
  - Dun - Dunl (Box 63)
  - Dunbar, Helen Flanders (Box 63)
  - Duncan (Box 63)
  - Duncan, Julian Smith (Box 63)
  - Dunham, Harold H. (Box 63)
  - Dunkel, Wilbur Dwight (Box 63)
  - Dunkman, William Edward (Box 63)
  - Dunlap, Leslie W. (Box 63)
  - Dunn (Box 64)
  - Dunn, Charles Wesley (Box 64)
  - Dunn, Frederick Sherwood (Box 64)
  - Dunning, John Ray & Hermon Waldo Farwell (Box 64)
  - Dunning, William Archibald & Joseph Gregoire de Roulhac Hamilton (Box 64)
  - Dunning, William Bailey (Box 64)
  - Dunp. Dup (Box 64)
  - Dupriez, Leon Hugo (Box 64)
  - Durbin, Evan Frank Mottram & John Bowlby (Box 64)
  - Durkin, Helen E., Kenriette Glatzer, & Janette S. Hirsch (Box 64)
  - Durling, Dwight L (Box 64)
  - Dutton, Meiric K. (Box 64)
  - Duvall, Josephine (Box 64)
  - Dur - Duw (Box 64)
  - Dw - Dz (Box 64)
  - Dykstra, Clarence Addison (Box 64)
  - Ea (Box 65)
  - Earle, Edward Mead (Box 65)
  - Earle, Mortimer Lamson (Box 65)
  - Easton, Stewart Copinger (Box 65)
  - Eastwood, Robert Parker (Box 65)
  - Eaton (Box 65)
  - Eb (Box 65)
  - Ebenstein, William (Box 65)
  - Ec... (Box 65)
  - Echardt, Arthur Roy (Box 65)
  - Eckert (Box 65)
  - Economics of Public Policy Series (Box 65)
  - Economic Reconstruction (Box 65)
  - Ed - Edi (Box 65)
  - Eddy (Box 65)
  - Edelman, Nathan (Box 65)
  - Edelstein, David Simeon (Box 65)
  - Edm - Eds (Box 65)
  - Edman, Irwin (Box 65)
  - The Educational Directory (Box 65)
  - Ee - Ef (Box 66)
  - Edwards (Box 66)
  - Edwards, Corwin D. (Box 66)
  - Efros, Israel Isaac (Box 66)
  - Eg - Eh (Box 66)
  - Ehrenpreis, Irvin (Box 66)
  - Ei - Em (Box 66)
  - Eide, Richard Benjamin (Box 66)
  - Eigerman, Hyman (Box 66)
  - Eilers, Ralph M. (Box 66)
  - Einstein, Lewis David (Box 66)
  - Eis. (Box 67)
  - Eiselen, Frederick Carl (Box 67)
  - Eisenberg, Azriel Louis (Box 67)
  - Eisenstein, Miriam (Box 67)
  - Eitan, Israel (Box 67)
  - Ekirch, Arthur Alphonse (Box 67)
  - Ela - Elk (Box 67)
  - Elbow, Matthew H. (Box 67)
  - Elder, Earl Edgar (Box 67)
  - Eldr(e)(i)dge (Box 67)
  - Ell - Eiz (Box 67)
  - Elliott (Box 67)
  - Elliott, Charlotte (Box 67)
  - Elliott, Edward Charles (Box 67)
  - Elliott, L. R. (Box 67)
  - Elliott, William Yandell (Box 67)
  - Ellison, Alfred (Box 67)
  - Elson, James Hinsdale (Box 67)
  - Em (Box 68)
  - Emelianoff, Ivan V. (Box 68)
  - Emerton, Ephraim (Box 68)
  - En - Enf (Box 68)
  - Encyclopedia of Food (Box 68)
  - Eng (Box 68)
  - Engberg, Robert M. (Box 68)
  - Engel, Eugene W. (Box 68)
  - England, F. E. (Box 68)
  - English Institute Annual (Box 68)
  - English Institute Essays (Box 68)
  - Enn - Ep (Box 69)
  - Epler, Stephen Edward (Box 69)
  - Epstean, Edward (Box 69)
  - Er - En (Box 69)
  - Ergang, Robert Reinhold (Box 69)
  - Ericsson, Emily (Box 69)
  - Erk - Erv (Box 69)
  - Ernst, Robert (Box 69)
  - Erskine, Helen (Box 69)
  - Erskine, John (Box 69)
  - Ertl, Tell (Box 69)
  - Es - Eu (Box 70)
  - Europa Publications (Box 70)
  - Evans (Box 70)
  - Evans, Anastasia H. (Box 70)
  - Evans, Austin Patterson (Box 70)
  - Evans, Bergen & George J. Mohr (Box 70)
  - Everest, Allan Seymour (Box 70)
  - Everett (Box 70)
  - Everett, Charles Warren (Box 70)
  - Everett, John Rutherford (Box 70)
  - Everett, E.B. (Box 70)
  - Everett, Samuel (Box 70)
  - Everson, Ida Gertrude (Box 70)
  - Eves, Charles Kenneth (Box 71)
  - Ew-Ex (Box 71)
  - Even, Frederic (Box 71)
  - Eyck, Erich (Box 71)
  - Fa - Fai (Box 71)
  - Fackenthal, Frank Diehi (Box 71)
  - Facsimile Text Society (Box 71)
  - Faggett, Harry Lee (Box 71)
  - Fairchild, Hoxie Neale (Box 71)
  - Fal - Fan (Box 72)
  - Falck, Edward (Box 72)
  - Fames, Oscar Julius (Box 72)
  - Far - Farq (Box 72)
  - Far Eastern Quarterly (Box 72)
  - Fargo, Lucile Foster (Box 72)
  - Farmer, Paul (Box 72)
  - Farnsworth, William Oliver (Box 72)
  - Farr - Farw (Box 73)
  - Farrar, Kathryn & Albert Joseph Kennedy (Box 73)
  - Farrar & Reinhart, Inc. (Box 73)
  - Fas - Fay (Box 73)
  - Faught, Millard Clark (Box 73)
  - Fay, Eliot G. (Box 73)
  - Fe - Fei (Box 73)
  - Fedden, Katharine Waldo Douglas Hunter (Box 73)
  - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America (Box 73)
  - Fel - Fen (Box 73)
  - Feleky, Antoinette (Box 73)
  - Fer - Feu (Box 74)
  - Ferrari, Robert (Box 74)
  - Ferriss, Hugh (Box 74)
  - Fi - Fil (Box 74)
  - Field, Minna (Box 74)
  - Fields, Victor Alexander (Box 74)
  - Fife, Robert Herndon (Box 74)
  - Filler, Louis (Box 74)
  - Fin (Box 74)
  - Finch, James Kip (Box 74)
  - Fine, Sherwood Monroe (Box 74)
  - Fine Arts Series (Box 74)
  - Finkelstein, Herman Norman (Box 74)
  - Finkelstein, Louis (Box 74)
  - Finn - Fir (Box 75)
  - Finney, Katherine (Box 75)
  - Fis. (Box 75)
  - Fisher (Box 75)
  - Fisher, Mitchell Salem (Box 75)
  - Fit - Fiv (Box 75)
  - Fitch, John Andrews (Box 75)
  - Fite, Emerson D. (Box 75)
  - Fitzgerald, Margaret Mary (Box 75)
  - Fitzpatrick, Edward Augustus (Box 75)
  - Fla. (Box 75)
  - Fle. (Box 75)
  - Fleming, Denna Frank (Box 75)
  - Fleming, Wallace Bruce (Box 75)
  - Fleming, Walter Lynwood (Box 75)
  - Fletcher (Box 75)
  - Fletcher, Jefferson Butler (Box 75)
  - Fletcher, Raymond (Box 75)
  - Flexner, Abraham (Box 75)
  - Fli (Box 76)
  - Flick, Alexander Clarence (Box 76)
  - Flo-Fly (Box 76)
  - Flournoy, Francis Rosebro (Box 76)
  - Faa, Bruno (Box 76)
  - Fod. - Fon (Box 76)
  - Fogle, French Rowe (Box 76)
  - Folger Shakespeare Library publications (Box 76)
  - Fora - Fore (Box 76)
  - Ford. (Box 76)
  - Forester, Max (Box 76)
  - Forg - Fors (Box 76)
  - Forman, Sidney (Box 76)
  - Fortune, Reo Franklin (Box 76)
  - Fos - Fot (Box 76)
  - Fosdick, Dorothy (Box 76)
  - Foster, Robert Geib & Pauline Park Wilson (Box 76)
  - Foster, Finley Melville Kendall (Box 76)
  - Fou - Fow (Box 76)
  - Foundations of Democracy (Box 76)
  - Fowler, Dorothy Ganfield (Box 76)
  - Fowler, George Bingham (Box 76)
  - Fox, Dixon Ryan (Box 77)
  - Fox, Grace (Box 77)
  - Fox, Lorene Kimball (Box 77)
  - Fox (Box 77)
  - Frachtenberg, Leo Joachim (Box 77)
  - Fradkin, Elvira K. (Box 77)
  - Frae - Fram (Box 77)
  - Frame, Donald Murdoch (Box 77)
  - Fran - Fraz (Box 77)
  - Frank, Arthur De Witt (Box 77)
  - Frank, Edgar B. (Box 77)
  - Frankel, Charles (Box 77)
  - Frankenberg, Lloyd (Box 77)
  - Frankfort, Henri (Box 77)
  - Fraser (Box 77)
  - Fraser, Ian Forbes (Box 77)
  - Fraser, Mowat Gjems (Box 77)
  - Fred - Frei (Box 78)
  - Freeburg, Victor Oscar (Box 78)
  - Freedman, Florence B. (Box 78)
  - Fren - Frey (Box 78)
  - Freienmuth von Helms, E. (Box 78)
  - French, David Garfield (Box 78)
  - French, J. Milton & Clayton M. Hall (Box 78)
  - Freund., Ernst (Box 78)
  - Freund., Ludwig (Box 78)
  - Freund., Philip (Box 78)
  - Freyre, GIlberto (Box 78)
  - Fri (Box 78)
  - Fridenberg, Percy Henry (Box 78)
  - Fried, B.M. (Box 78)
  - Friedenberg, Janice (Box 78)
  - Friedi, Berthold. C. (Box 78)
  - Fritz, Kurt von (Box 78)
  - Fro - Fry (Box 78)
  - Fromm, Erich (Box 78)
  - Frost, James Arthur (Box 78)
  - Fu - Fuh (Box 78)
  - Fuess, Claude Moore (Box 78)
  - Fuller (Box 78)
  - Fun - Fus (Box 78)
  - Funk, Arthur Layton (Box 78)
  - Ga - Gai (Box 79)
  - Gagey, Edmond McAdoo (Box 79)
  - Gaines, Francis Pendleton (Box 79)
  - Gaines, Ruth (Box 79)
  - Gal (Box 79)
  - Galarza, Ernesto (Box 79)
  - Galdston, lago (Box 79)
  - Galenson, Walter (Box 79)
  - Gall, Morris (Box 79)
  - Gallagher, Buell Gordon (Box 79)
  - Gallagher, Helen Mar Pierce (Box 79)
  - Gallaudet, Bern Budd (Box 79)
  - Gam - Gan (Box 80)
  - Gamble (Box 80)
  - Gambs, John Sake (Box 80)
  - Gann, Edith (Box 80)
  - Gantenbein, James Watson (Box 80)
  - Gar (Box 81)
  - Garceau, Oliver (Box 81)
  - Garcia (Box 81)
  - Gardner, William Bradford (Box 81)
  - Garlan, Edwin Norman (Box 81)
  - Garn - Gary (Box 81)
  - Garnett, A. Campbell (Box 81)
  - Garnett, Christopher Browne (Box 81)
  - Garnett, Wilma Leslie (Box 81)
  - Garraty, John Arthur (Box 81)
  - Garst, Robert Edward & Theodore Menline Bernstein (Box 81)
  - Gas (Box 81)
  - Gautier, mile Felix & Dorothy Ford Mayhew (Box 81)
  - Gay - Gay (Box 82)
  - Gay, Peter Jack (Box 82)
  - Gayer, Arthur David, Paul T. Homan, & Earle K. James (Box 82)
  - Gea - Gei (Box 82)
  - Gel - Gep (Box 82)
  - George, Albert Joseph (Box 82)
  - Ger (Box 82)
  - Gerard, Raoul (Box 82)
  - Gerber, William (Box 82)
  - Geshkoff, Theodore Ivanoff (Box 82)
  - Gewirth, Alan (Box 82)
  - Gib - Giff (Box 82)
  - Gibson (Box 82)
  - Gibson, Florence Elizabeth (Box 82)
  - Gibson, Roland (Box 82)
  - Gignilliat, George Warren (Box 82)
  - Gilbert (Box 83)
  - Gildersleeve, Virginia Crocheron (Box 83)
  - Gile - Gilk (Box 83)
  - Giles, Herbert Allen (Box 83)
  - Gilfillan, S. Colum (Box 83)
  - Gill - Gin (Box 83)
  - Gillain, Cornelius W. (Box 83)
  - Gillen, Paul Bates (Box 83)
  - Gi (Box 83)
  - Gillett, Charles Ripley (Box 83)
  - Gillim, Marion Hamilton (Box 83)
  - Gilman, Margaret (Box 83)
  - Ginzberg, Eli (Box 83)
  - Gipson, Richard McCandless (Box 84)
  - Gir - Git (Box 84)
  - Girardin, Rena de (Box 84)
  - Gla - Gle (Box 84)
  - Glenn, Garrard & A. Arthur Schiller (Box 84)
  - Gli - Glu (Box 84)
  - Glueck, Eleanor Touroff (Box 84)
  - Gob - Goi (Box 84)
  - Goble, George Washington (Box 84)
  - Gode-von Aesch, Alexander (Box 84)
  - Goebel, Julius Ludwig (Box 84)
  - Gohdes, Clarence Louis Frank (Box 84)
  - Gol - Go (Box 84)
  - Gold, Bela (Box 84)
  - Golde - Goldm (Box 85)
  - Goldfeld, Abraham (Box 85)
  - Goldmann, Franz (Box 85)
  - Golds - Gon (Box 85)
  - Goldstein (Box 85)
  - Good-Goodell (Box 85)
  - Goodhart, Simon Philip & Benjamin Harris Balser (Box 85)
  - Goodman (Box 85)
  - Goodman, Louis Sandford. (Box 85)
  - Goodman, Paul & Percival Goodman (Box 85)
  - Goodnow, Frank Johnson (Box 85)
  - Goodr - Goo (Box 85)
  - Goodrich, Chauncy & Luther Carrington Goodrich (Box 85)
  - Goodwin, George Munro (Box 85)
  - Gor. (Box 85)
  - Goran, Morris (Box 85)
  - Gordon (Box 85)
  - Gordon, Antoinette K. (Mrs Milton J.) (Box 85)
  - Gordon, Donald Craigie (Box 86)
  - Gordon, Douglas H. & Norman Lewis Torrey (Box 86)
  - Gordon, Philip (Box 86)
  - Gordon, Wendell Chaffee (Box 86)
  - Gorfinkle, Jospeh I (Box 86)
  - Gosnell, Harold F. (Box 86)
  - Got - Gov (Box 86)
  - Gove, Philip Babcock (Box 86)
  - Governmental Affairs Institute (Box 86)
  - Grab - Graf (Box 86)
  - Graber, Doris Appel (Box 86)
  - Grace Episcopal Church, Orange, N.J. (Box 86)
  - Grady, George, Press, Inc. (Box 86)
  - Graham (Box 86)
  - Graham, Walter James (Box 86)
  - Grainger (Box 86)
  - Gran. (Box 86)
  - Granger, Edith Granger's index to poetry (Box 86)
  - Grant (Box 86)
  - Graves (Box 86)
  - Gray (Box 87)
  - Gray, Charles Harold (Box 87)
  - Gray, Louis Herbert (Box 87)
  - Gray, Roland (Box 87)
  - Gray (Box 87)
  - Grea - Greel (Box 87)
  - Grebler, Leo (Box 87)
  - Greek literature (Box 87)
  - Green (Box 87)
  - Green, Adwin Wigfall (Box 87)
  - Green, Alexander (Box 87)
  - Green, Helen D. (Box 87)
  - Green, Mary McBurney (Box 87)
  - Greenberg, Sidney (Box 87)